Open the well-treated famous line texture
The texture in the picture is continuously transparent
Image size
Unit size is changed to inches
The length of the famous line is determined by SPI value
SPI means how many frames are there in one inch
You can set the width of the picture to the corresponding number of inches
At the same time, pay attention to the height of the picture
Save the PNG picture
Then click Save
Here I don't need to save, click Cancel
Come to the software
Newly build a famous line
Switch to the well-treated famous line
First skip some value settings
Add the well-treated picture
Because the width of the picture is 0.5 inches
Then there will be two frames in 1 inch
Choose SPIR
Switch to the thin unit of the line
See 8.89 mm
This value will affect the setting of the well-treated
Here just write a value
Use free famous line
Add the famous line to the board
Enlarge the details of the 3D window
If you want the famous line to be cut with the board
Set the value of the well-treated to half the height of the famous line
See the overall effect
Use the auto-generated PBR sticker to generate the well-treated image
Click to generate the well-treated image
Click the browse button
The well-treated image is upside down
Turn off
The well-treated strength is changed to negative
Enlarge the famous line to check
There is a small crack between the well-treated picture
Switch to the well-treated image
Show the very well-treated image
Now the famous line is cut
It has theтора